Dawid Dąbrowski

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am fascinated by the possibilities of front-end development and want to use my skills to create interactive and user-friendly applications. I am confident that as a Front-end Developer I will have the opportunity to continuously develop and gain new experiences, which is extremely important to me.

EXPERIENCE

FOA Game Tester

Keywords Studios 07.2022 - present

- Developing scenarios and test cases
- Exploratory tests
- · Regression testing
- Independent bugs cause analysis.
- · Working with the development team
- Finding and reporting defects in Jira
- · Working in Agile environment

Independent administrative office employee

Silesian University of Technology

02.2020 - 06.2022

- Working with database systems
- Supervision of documentation
- Administration of majors for students from foreign countries

COURSES

Front-end Developer [React] course

09.01.2023 - present

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Physical Education AWF in Katowice

2016-2019

IT Technician school

2012-2016



CONTACT



501 218 804



dabrowskidawid680@gmail.com



github.com/dawiddabrowskii



in linkedin.com/in/dawid-dabrowski680

TOOLS

- React
- JavaScript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- SCSS
- Bootstrap5
- GIT
- Jira
- Confluence

SKILLS

- · Ability to work in an international environment
- Analytical thinking
- · Good work organization
- · Creativity in search of solutions

LANGUAGES

- Enalish B2/C1
- Polish native

INTERESTS

- Gaming industry
- Strenght training
- Football